ashmax.com 2012-07-15

# AshMax Disclaimer | ASHMAX

In **AshMax** we are committed to protecting your privacy.   
as we understand privacy is a primary concern today, on and off the Internet. We are aware of these concerns and want you to feel comfortable visiting our site.

**AshMax Company** provides a free registration for affiliates whom are interested in building multiple streams of income from online opportunities.  
**AshMax** Strives to provide you with many internet-success advantages. 

**AshMax** is committed to implementing measures designed to respect and protect the privacy of our members. We will never sell, bargain, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period!

In AshMax we receive some basic information from our members, and will never release, sell or share personally identifiable information about our users without their permission.

Please note that we review and modify our privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices are therefore subject to change.

We recommend that you periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. 

To contact us about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [**admin@ashmax.com**](mailto:admin@ashmax.com)

We gather non-personally identifiable information about the members and visitors of our site:  
that helps us, among other things, to monitor our internal operations, to improve our features, and determine the effectiveness of our system and promotional activities.  
We may also use cookies which allow us to serve visitors of our site better and more efficiently.

Our members may choose to "opt out" of receiving any communications, or promotional materials directly related to our program provided by us and our affiliates.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you.  
We expect our partners, members, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users and visitors.

We also may use personally identifiable information for this site (such as email address, name, etc) to communicate with you regarding your account, registration or your progress, and we may occasionally inform you of new features, services, promotions, events and possible additions to our site.  
We limit our own e-mail solicitations to us and those registered members/affiliates who have not "opted out" of receiving such communications.

Our communications are limited in to ways that we clearly indicate!

You have the ability to change or correct certain information in our data records, such as your contact information by signing into Your [**Members Area**](http://ashmax.com/members) and going to " **My Profile** ". 

You may change this information at any time.   
If you have any questions about correcting or changing your information, please contact us at: [**admin@ashmax.com**](mailto:admin@ashmax.com)
